Guide to the Paul Kwilecki Photographs and Papers, 1960-2008 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials Series, 1960-2001 (bulk 1970s-1990s) and undated
  - Religion, (8 folders)
    - Interior of Antioch Baptist Church on Lake Douglas Road, 1975, unnumbered (Box PHO 6)
    - Privy behind Moses Chapel, near Recovery, Decatur County, 1989 Nov., 55-1189-7 (Box PHO 6)
    - Rev. Jeffrey baptizing at Mt. Zion. Decatur County, 1981 July, 94-781-28 (Box PHO 6)
    - Second print of privy behind Moses Chapel, above, 1989 Nov., 55-1189-6 (Box PHO 6)
    - Window in First Presbyterian Church, Bainbridge, seen from outside, 1979 Jan., 13-179 (Box PHO 6)
    - Consecration service prior to Sunday morning service. St. Mary's, near Baconton, Mitchell Co., Ga., 1984 Feb., 11-284-33 (Box PHO 6)
    - Pilgrim Rest A.M.E.Church. Old structure and new building, 1985 Apr., 16-485-10 (Box PHO 6)
      The old structure has been torn down.
    - Rev. Jeffry in the living room of his home, West Bainbridge, Ga., 1982 Sept., 89-982-5 (Box PHO 6)
    - First baptism in Mt. Zuma pool, 1982 Apr., 38-482-24a (Box PHO 6)
    - Rev. Lois Hurst with congregants, Mitchell Co., 1984 July, 42-784 (Box PHO 6)
    - Rev. Mitchell baptizing at last night of revival, Mt. Zuma, 1991 Apr., 8-491-23 (Box PHO 6)
    - Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church revival, group of two photographs:
      - Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1977 May, 1: 29-577-16 (Box PHO 6)
        This is a set of pictures made at a revival. Supper was served first, then singing and guitar playing. Then preaching. Note the faces.
      - Gospel singers at Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1977 May, 2: 29-577-20a (Box PHO 6)
    - Window in First Baptist Church, Bainbridge (5 x 7), circa 1968, unnumbered (Box PHO 6)
    - New Hope Missionary Baptist Church, West Bainbridge, Ga., 1982 Apr., 43-482-17a (Box PHO 6)
    - Entrance to Mt. Zion Missionary Baptist Church, Cyrene, Ga., 1980 Feb., (Understandings), 11-280-2 (Box PHO 6)
    - Privy and pew in church yard. St. Luke, Faceville, Ga., 1980 Oct. (Understandings), 97-1080-7 (Box PHO 6)
    - Moses Chapel, near Recovery, Ga., 1980 Feb. (Understandings), 16-280-4 (Box PHO 7)
    - Baptism pool in front yard of the Attapulgus African Baptist Church, 1980 Oct. (Understandings), 105-1080-6 (Box PHO 7)
    - Union Springs Primitive Baptist Church. Miller County, Ga., 1980 Nov. (Understandings), 117-1180-7 (Box PHO 7)
    - Rev. Lois Hurst, Assembly of God, Meigs, Ga., 1984 June, 40-684-9 (Box PHO 7)
    - Moses Chapel, near Recovery, Ga., 1982 Mar., 26-382-3 (Box PHO 7)
      This is a beautiful old church in a stereotypical southern setting. However, it was moved to its present location about thirty years ago from an area that was being inundated by Jim Woodruf Dam. It is no longer in use.
    - Nearing the end of the foot washing service, 1983 Nov., 69-1183-16a (Box PHO 7)
      This is an emotional ceremony and the woman dancing is having an ecstatic experience.
    - Moses Chapel seen from the rear, near Recovery, Ga., 1989 Nov., 54-1189-17 (Box PHO 7)
    - Mt. Horum, northeast of Climax, Ga., 1983 Dec., 1: 75-1283 (Box PHO 7)
      This is the first image in a group of six that tells the story of Mt. Horum. Once a relatively active congregation, it declined until finally one Sunday the worshipers left and never came back. The altar, pews, even the prayer books remain, but the grounds are grown up in weeds and saplings.
    - Mt. Horum interior, 1978 Dec., 2: 124-1278-12a (Box PHO 7)
    - Mt. Horum interior, 1978 Dec., 3: 124-1278-7a (Box PHO 7)
    - Mt. Horum, 1989 May, 4: 27-589-20 (Box PHO 7)
      In this shot the vine indicates the disuse the church has fallen into. Also note the chain on the door is the same throughout all the picture.
    - Mt. Horum, 1991 May, 5: 10-591-15 (Box PHO 7)
      This is a recent interior shot showing how the church was left. I did not touch or arrange anything. However, I was extremely cautious getting in through a window. The largest diamondback rattlesnake I ever saw was killed less than a mile from this location.
    - Mt. Horum, 1991 Mar., 6: 5-391-22 (Box PHO 7)
      The final shot in the series. Compare this to the first picture. The building is askew, but little else is different.
    - Covered dish supper after revival, 1977 May, 30-577-8a (Box PHO 7)
    - Tent revival, 1981 Sept., 117-981-13 (Box PHO 7)
    - The wedding of Brenda Mitchell, 1983 Sept., 46-983-28 (Box PHO 7)
      Rev. Mitchell is an attendant; his brother, a minister from Thomasville, officiated.
    - Interior of Sunday School, Pilgrim Rest A.M.E. Church just off West River Road, 1980 Oct., 102-1080-10 (Box PHO 7)
    - Wedding ceremony, mother of the groom, 1983 Sept., 47-983-17 (Box PHO 7)
    - Sunday School of God's Tabernacle just off Lake Douglas Road, 1986 Nov., 22-1186-9 (Box PHO 7)
    - Sunday school class and minister on steps, Mt. Zion A.M.E. Church, 1981 Aug., 106-881-3 (Box PHO 7)
      See my notes for a fuller description of this photo.
    - God's Tabernacle, 1986 Nov., 23-1186-5 (Box PHO 7)
      Back row: the minister and assistant minister. The man in front is serving his apprenticeship. They are strong, dedicated individuals.
    - Brenda Mitchell, her husband, and Reginald, their son, in their mobile home, 1985 Nov., 50-1185-12 (Box PHO 7)
      I photographed their wedding (she is Rev. Mitchell's daughter) a couple of years before. The husband works as a mechanic for Kmart but wants to be a preacher like his father-in-law.
    - Bishop, Church of God in Christ, 1997 Nov., 44-1197-27 (Box PHO 7)
    - Minister and Sunday School class cleaning out baptismal pool (PZ will look up name of church later - remind him), 1997 July, 17-797-9a (Box PHO 7)
    - Boy and girl behind New Abundant Life sign (remind PZ - look up name of church), 1997 Aug., 19-897-24 (Box PHO 7)
    - New minister at Nelson Chapel AME Church, 1997 Aug., 23-897-14 (Box PHO 7)
    - Minister in white with crosses (remind PZ - look up name of church), 1997 Aug., 19-897-12 (Box PHO 7)
    - Minister, Church of God in Christ, 1997 Nov., 44-1197-6a (Box PHO 7)
    - Store front church, 1986 Oct., 19-1086-3 (Box PHO 7)
    - Interior, Sunday morning, Fellowship of Faith church, 1997 Aug., 20-897-17a (Box PHO 7)
    - Interior of Church of God in Christ, women singing, 1997 Nov., 45-1197-23 (Box PHO 7)
    - Night exterior of Fellowship of Faith church, 1997 Feb., 5-297-17a (Box PHO 7)
    - Night shot of St. Luke Free Will Baptist Church, 1997 Feb., 6-297-10 (Box PHO 7)
    - Cornerstone Baptist Church (formerly a filling station), 1997 June, 14-697-33 (Box PHO 7)
    - Easter Sunday, First Methodist Church, 1995 Apr., 1-495-32 (Box PHO 7)
    - Minister, Fellowship of Faith Curch, 1994 May, 14-594-5 (Box PHO 7)
    - Easter Sunday, First Methodist Church, 1995 Apr., 2-495-10 (Box PHO 7)
    - Street preacher, Beecher Thomas, with New Testament in his pocket, 1994 Mar., 7-394-15 (Box PHO 7)
    - Sunday School teacher outside First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May, 12-594-17 (Box PHO 7)
    - Sunday School student on steps, First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May, 12-594-28 (Box PHO 7)
    - Couple standing in front of First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May, 12-594-22 (Box PHO 7)
    - Man and woman ascending steps of First A.B. Church, Bainbridge, 1994 May, 12-594-25 (Box PHO 7)
    - Woman on steps of First Methodist Church, Bainbridge, 1994 Apr., 8-494-25 (Box PHO 7)
    - Church front, Brinson, Ga., 1996 Feb., 6-296-18 (Box PHO 7)
    - House of worship, West Bainbridge, 2000 Feb., 4-200-20 (Box PHO 7)
    - Church for sale, 1998 Apr., 22-498-20 (Box PHO 7)
    - Communion service, Nelson Chapel, A.M.E. Church, 1998 Mar., 14-398-18 (Box PHO 7)
    - 129th anniversary ceremony, Nelson Chapel, A.M.E. Church, 1998 Mar., 12-398-4a (Box PHO 7)
    - 129th anniversary ceremony, Nelson Chapel, A.M.E. Church, 1998 Mar., 12-398-23 (Box PHO 7)
  - Shoppers, (2 folders)
    - Blind man being assisted in his grocery buying by friend, 1980 Apr. (Understandings), 38-480-2 (Box PHO 8)
    - Preparing to enter the Bargain Center, 1978 July (Understandings), 49-778-25 (Box PHO 8)
    - At checkout, 1980 Mar. (Understandings), 26-380-9a (Box PHO 8)
    - At Elmore's department store, 1981 Aug., 99-881-16a (Box PHO 8)
    - Waiting at checkout, 1980 Mar., 24-380-3 (Box PHO 8)
    - Claustrophobic grocery store, 1982 Mar., 18-382-13a (Box PHO 8)
    - Second print of At checkout, above, 1980 Mar., 26-380-9a (Box PHO 8)
    - Visiting, 1978 Sept., 75-978-15 (Box PHO 8)
    - Typical shopper, 1980 Mar. (Understandings), 28-380-19 (Box PHO 8)
      Typical shopper with forlorn, absent-minded look on her face, which you see everywhere when shoppers are preoccupied.
    - Woman putting bacon in grocery cart, 1980, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
    - Gossip, Wynn-Dixie Grocery, 1981 Aug., 101-881-21a (Box PHO 8)
    - Women waiting in line at grocery store for checkout, 1980 Feb. (Understandings), 19-280-3 (Box PHO 8)
    - Shoppers, 1981 Jan., 16-181-2 (Box PHO 8)
      People don't realize how they look when they're preoccupied with shopping. I set about to photograph their expressions which are those of a stalker.
    - What an expression! 1981 Dec., 145-1281-3a (Box PHO 8)
    - Woman crossing Broad Street, 1979 June, 94-679-15 (Box PHO 8)
      Note the fan she carries with her.
    - Grocery buying, 1980 Mar., 28-380-18 (Box PHO 8)
  - Shade Tobacco, (2 folders)
    - Putting up the shades, 1962, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      This was one of the earliest pictures I made that pleased me. Even so the exposure leaves something to be desired.
    - Woman sitting in front of tobacco shack, 1963, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      Typical tobacco shack in which workers lived. Woman is trying to get warm in the sunshine.
    - Front porch of two-family tobacco tenant house, 1964 (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      A duplex shack in which two families live. Shade tobacco is used as the wrapper for cigars. The leaf has to be absolutely perfect.
    - Three workers resting on benches under shade, 1965, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      Workers resting in field. They are in the process of stringing the plants up.
    - Woman hoeing tobacco plants, 1965, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      Woman hoeing tender new plants. Note the layers of clothes she is wearing.
    - Workers resting under shades, 1965, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
    - Man with cigarette picking leaves, 1966, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      Worker picking leaves. Lowest leaves are picked first. Leaves are stacked on a wagon and hauled to barn to cure.
    - Two women (head shot) in front of tobacco barn, 1966 (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      Two women resting outside barn.
    - Men shooting craps in the field while they wait for the wagon to return, W.B. Miller and Son farm (1), 1966, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
    - Men shooting craps in the field while they wait for the wagon to return, W.B. Miller and Son farm (2), 1966, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
    - Shade tobacco workers shooting craps., [3] (Box PHO 8)
    - Stringer inside barn, 1968 (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
    - Three children on floor of tobacco barn, 1968, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      These are children of the women working just out of camera range, stringing tobacco inside the cool, cathedral-like barns. They play all day on the dirt floor. Their mothers are stringing leaves which will be hung in the barn ceiling to cure.
    - Woman sewing shades, 1968 (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
    - Willie James Igler, tobacco worker, 1968, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      He was a worker and foreman. This picture was taken at his home. He had eleven children and several grandchildren.
    - Two boys hiding in tobacco leaves, 1971, unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      These children do not pick leaves despite their having boards in their hands. They are playing under the ripe, aromatic plants. Their jobs were to do odds and ends.
    - In the wake of shade tobacco, 1982 Oct., 94-1082-5 (Box PHO 8)
    - In the wake of shade tobacco, 1982 Sept., 86-982-22 (Box PHO 8)
    - Tobacco hand's house, 1982 Aug., 20-882-23a (Box PHO 8)
      Tobacco hand's house long after tobacco had ceased to be grown in Decatur County. Such places by 1980 were the worst of slums.
    - Man standing on front porch, 1982 Sept., 87-982-11 (Box PHO 8)
  - Social Events, (1 folder)
    - Wedding reception at the bride's home, 1976 Sept., 117-976-9 (Box PHO 8)
    - Woman with plate at reception, 1976 Sept. (117-976?), unnumbered (Box PHO 8)
      A wedding reception for Chris Dollar.
  - Stores, (1 folder)
    - Mrs. Tomlinson in the house of tomatoes, 1967, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
    - Ms. Bennet in her jewelry store on West Street, 1978 Oct. (Understandings), 89-1078-9 (Box PHO 9)
    - Window display in McCrory's 5 cent and 10 cent store, 1978 Nov. (Understandings), 102-1178 (Box PHO 9)
    - Outside entrance to Wynn's Department Store, 1968 Dec., unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
    - Ms. Sasser in her grocery store, 1979 Oct.(Understandings), 135-1079-22 (Box PHO 9)
    - Interior of Jake's Pawn Shop on Water Street, 1968, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
      Young man is making a weekly payment.
    - Religious pictures for sale at Elmore's Department Store, 1978 Nov., 103-1178 10a (Box PHO 9)
    - Mr. Gause in his Pure Oil Station, 1980 May, 49-580-12a (Box PHO 9)
    - Hart-Rollins Furniture Co. Broad Street, 1981 Jan., 16-181-15 (Box PHO 9)
    - Façade of the Men's Shop, 1970, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
      Originally operated by Willie Jim Brockett.
    - Broad Street, McCrory's Diana Shops, 1967, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
      View of Broad Street from Willis Park.
    - Neighborhood grocery and meat market, 1987 Aug., 9-887-34 (Box PHO 9)
    - 1981 Mar., 37-381-26 (Box PHO 9)
      Tiny store near school in West Bainbridge where children go to buy candy, etc. Also neighborhood grocery. This is the proprietor.
    - Mr. Ward in the window of his hardware store, 1968, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
  - Swine Time, (1 folder)
    - Swine Time. Climax, Ga., 1980 Nov. (Understandings), 106-1180-19 (Box PHO 9)
    - Two politicians and a preacher. Which is which? 1980 Nov. (Understandings), 118-1180-25a (Box PHO 9)
    - Junk table with women, 1975 Nov. (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
    - Houses, tents and umbrellas, 1975, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
      People listening to and watching the hog calling contest.
    - A table of secondhand wares for sale. Typical junk, 1979 Nov., 151-1179-3a (Box PHO 9)
  - Trailways Bus Station, (1 folder)
    - Woman, boy, juke box, 1978 (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1978 Aug., 56-878-33 (Box PHO 9)
    - Family, Trailways Bus Station, 1978 May, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
    - Exterior, Trailways Bus Station, 1977 Nov., 130-1177-20 (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1978 Sept., 70-978-23 (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1977 Sept., 104-977-7a (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1980 July (Understandings), 65-780-12 (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1978 Jan. (Understandings), 1-1-78-23a (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1977 Dec., 138-1277-35 (Box PHO 9)
    - Trailways Bus Station, 1978 Aug., 68-878-7.5 (Box PHO 9)
    - Colored waiting room. Trailways Bus Station, 1978 Jan., 1-1-78-5a (Box PHO 9)
    - Scales in the waiting room. Trailways Bus Station, 1980 Jan., 5-180-6 (Box PHO 9)
    - Phone,Trailways Bus station, 1978 Jan., 1-1-78-13A (Box PHO 9)
  - Workers, (2 folders)
    - Tenant farmer resting in his front yard, 1983 Apr., 18-483-26 (Box PHO 9)
      This is one of my favorite photographs. See my notes for more information on this man.
    - Watt Baldwin, Jr. in his garage, 1980 June, 59-680-23a (Box PHO 9)
    - Log yard worker on a fork lift, 1990 May, 10-590-32 (Box PHO 9)
      Log yards broker pulp wood between the grower and the consumer (paper mills).
    - Man in weigh-in station at Elberta Crate and Box Co., 1984 May, 29-584 (Box PHO 9)
    - Elberta Crate and Box Co., 1981 Nov., 134-1181-8 (Box PHO 9)
    - Construction worker tearing down an old building (Belks), 1983 Oct., 49-1083-26 (Box PHO 9)
    - Livestock auction, 1982 Mar., 23-382-20 (Box PHO 9)
    - Tractor driver standing inside peanut warehouse, 1989 June, 43-989-7a (Box PHO 9)
      Pile of peanuts is visible behind him.
    - Fork lift operator on a log yard, 1989 Jan., 1-1-89 (Box PHO 9)
    - Elberta Crate and Box Co., 1981 Nov., 134-1181-7 (Box PHO 9)
    - Dollar Farm Products Co., 1989 Aug., 40-889-25 (Box PHO 9)
      This man drives a tractor during peanut season and a truck the rest of the year.
    - Dollar Farm Products Co., 1989 Aug., 38-889-32 (Box PHO 9)
      This man has been on top of a rail car loading corn from storage bins.
    - Elberta Crate and Box Co., 1982 Jan., 2-182-32 (Box PHO 9)
    - Man in field holding basket of bell peppers. Decatur County, 1984 June, 34-684 (Box PHO 9)
    - Resting in the field, 1983 July, 36-783-26a (Box PHO 9)
      Resting in the field while the big machine turns around at the end of a row.
    - Picking bell peppers, 1984 June, 37-684-9 (Box PHO 9)
    - Bell pepper pickers, 1984 June, 38-684-25A (Box PHO 9)
    - Maids in a room of the Stephen Decatur Hotel shortly before it was torn down, 1970, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
    - Prostitute standing in doorway of her house, 1965, No# (Box PHO 9)
      The building is the oldest structure in Bainbridge, so this is a picture of the oldest profession in front of the oldest building. Is she eyeing me as a prospective customer or just sizing me up?
    - Dr. M. A. Ehrlich in the doorway of his office, 1980 Aug., 78-880-11 (Box PHO 9)
    - Cecil Mills in his barbershop, 1970, unnumbered (Box PHO 9)
  - Willis Park, (2 folders)
    - Woman taking a picture of her son's company posed in front of the Confederate monument, 1989 May, 28-589-12 (Box PHO 10)
      The occasion was the dedication of a memorial to Vietnam veterans.
    - Man in phone booth, 1976 July (Understandings), 776-14 (Box PHO 10)
    - Men at Armistice Day ceremony, 1979 Nov. (Understandings), 156-1179-15a (Box PHO 10)
    - 1978 Sept., 71-978-6a (Box PHO 10)
      Before the park was redone people sat and watched and waited. Now the benches are gone and people only pass through the park.
    - Bike fest, 1999 June, 9-699-29 (Box PHO 10)
    - Mike Gast testing mike for spring festival, 1977 May (Understandings), 27-577-4a (Box PHO 10)
    - Bainbridge High School Band playing for some ceremony, 1976 Nov. (Understandings), 135-1176-9a (Box PHO 10)
    - Another view of the park, 1980 Apr., 38-480-32 (Box PHO 10)
    - Gospel singers in the gazebo on a Saturday afternoon, 1979 June (Understandings), 86-679 (Box PHO 10)
    - Willis Park United Daughters of the Confederacy posing under the statue on Confederate Memorial Day, 1974 (Understandings), unnumbered (Box PHO 10)
      A newspaper photographer was taking their picture.
    - Series of three photographs:
      This set shows a little girl (1) about to wet her pants, (2) wetting them under the watchful eye of the other children, and (3) she continues looking at the fish in the pool as though nothing had happened while the black children look to me for some reaction.
      - (1) Little girl wetting her pants, 1979 June, 76-679-27 (Box PHO 10)
      - (2) Little girl wetting her pants, 1979 June, 76-679-29 (Box PHO 10)
      - (3) Little girl wetting her pants, 1979 June, 76-679-30 (Box PHO 10)
    - Before the park was redone, 1980 Apr. (Understandings), 42-480-25 (Box PHO 10)
    - The Confederate statue in early morning fog, 1986 Feb., 8-286 (Box PHO 10)
    - British rowing team for 1996 Olympics, 1994 July, 19-794-29 (Box PHO 10)
    - Two veterans in front of gazebo, 1996 Nov., 42-1196-26 (Box PHO 10)
    - Wedding reception, Willis Park, 1989 Sept., 43-989-25a (Box PHO 10)
    - Armistice Day, Willis Park, 1969, 18 W.P. 3 (Box PHO 10)
    - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr., 29-498-15a (Box PHO 10)
    - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr., 30-498-28a (Box PHO 10)
    - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr., 30-498-17a (Box PHO 10)
    - Reenactment, Confederate Memorial Day, 1998 Apr., 30-498-14a (Box PHO 10)
    - [Veteran in the park], 2000, 10-9-2000-19 (Box PHO 10)
    - [Bainbridge High School Reunion], 2000, 13-9-2000-19 (Box PHO 10)
    - Santa in Willis Park, 2001 Dec., 27-1201-26 (Box PHO 10)
    - Children ready to march to the gazebo for wedding, Willis Park, 2001, 22-11-01 (Box PHO 10)
    - Willis Park series: Junior/Senior Prom, (3 folders)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May, 4-595-10 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May, 3-595-16 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May, 3-595-20 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May, 8-597-30 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May, 8-599-6 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May, 8-597-8 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May, 8-597-23 (Box PHO 10)
      - Couples posed on war memorial, 1998 May, 39-598-27 (Box PHO 10)
        Couples unwittingly posed by snapshooting mothers against the memorial to Decatur County men who have died in all wars since the Civil War.
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May, 38-598-16 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May, 6-599-24 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May, 38-598-31 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1990 May, 7-590-18(8) (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1996 May, 12-596-12 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May, 36-598-26 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May, 4-595-23 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May, 8-599-14 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May, 4-595-13 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1994 May, 13-594-29 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1997 May, 10-597-7 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May, 7-599-30 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1996 May, 12-596-18 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1995 May, 3-595-21 (Box PHO 10)
      - Spectator, Junior/Senior Prom, 1999 May, 8-599-28 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May, 38-598-13 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May, 39-598-13 (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, 1998 May, 40-598-18 (Box PHO 10)
      - [Spectators, Junior-Senior Prom], 2000, 8-5-00-10a (Box PHO 10)
        They are not applauding but fighting southern Georgia gnats.
      - A girl and her date, Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr., 3-4-01 (Box PHO 10)
      - Promenade begins, Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr., 3-4-01-24A (Box PHO 10)
      - Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr., 4-4-01 (Box PHO 10)
      - Spectators, Junior/Senior Prom, Willis Park, 2001 Apr., 4-4-01-27 (Box PHO 10)
  - Oversize Material Subseries
    Boxes house oversize photographic prints separated for housing from main series. Series structure is duplicated, beginning with Decatur Courthouse and ending with Workers. Also in the oversize section are six prints of Cape Cod shot in the 1960s by David Vestal, a friend and colleague of Paul Kwilecki.
    - Decatur County Court House Oversize Prints
      - Prisoners and guard working on dam, 1979, 1; unnumbered (Oversize-box 1)
        Chain gang guard watches prisoners building dam to keep water from overflowing highway. Typical swamp.
      - 1983 Mar., 13-383-28 (Oversize-box 1)
        This carcass has just been pulled out of the vat of hot water. The convicts have scraped the hide bare. Next step is to quarter.
      - Hog killing at the County Farm, 1983 Mar., 14-383-20a (Oversize-box 1)
        These men are rotating a hog carcass in hot water, preparatory to scraping the hair off the hide.
      - 1981 Dec., 142-1281-8 (Oversize-box 1)